8051projects.info 2016-11-24

# Privacy policy of 8051projects.info | Free Microcontroller Projects - 8051-AVR-PIC

**Free Microcontroller Projects - 8051-AVR-PIC**

[Home](http://www.8051projects.info/) [Forums](http://www.8051projects.info/forums/) >

### Privacy policy of 8051projects.info

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use 8051projects.info, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.  
8051projects.info strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.  
In order to use these forums, users are required to provide a username, password and e-mail address. Neither the Administrators of these forums, or the Moderators participating, are responsible for the privacy practices of any user. Remember that all information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to share any of your personal information. Any user who finds material posted by another user objectionable is encouraged to contact us via e-mail. 8051projects.info are authorized by you to remove or modify any data submitted by you to these forums for any reason we feel constitutes a violation of our policies, whether stated, implied or not.

**Personal Information**

8051projects.info collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis e.g. email address, name etc.  
This information is collected if you request information from us, Download files, and sign up to join our Forum or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.  
Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies must be turned on in your browser to participate as a user in these forums. Cookies are used here to hold your username, password and viewing and language options, allowing you to login.

**Ownership of Information**

8051projects.info is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

**Non-Personal Information**

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable e.g. using the sites automatic log files. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

**Release of Information**

If 8051projects.info is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.

**How You Can Correct or Remove Information**

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page.

**Updates and Effective Date**

8051projects.info reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy-practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

**Google Search Box**

The search box on this website (Search Box) is powered by Google Inc (Google). You acknowledge and agree that Google™s privacy policy (located at  http://www.google.co.in/intl/en/privacy.html) shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you consent to Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy.

**Google Ads** The Ads on this website is powered by Google Inc (Google). Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html)

**Agreeing to Terms**

If you do not agree to 8051projects.info Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.  
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

**Free Microcontroller Projects - 8051-AVR-PIC**

[Home](http://www.8051projects.info/) [Forums](http://www.8051projects.info/forums/) >
